

Vadym Kuznetsov, Full Stack Developer

Professional Web Developer with more than ten years of experience in areas such as the Internet of Things, sales, educational courses, etc. Worked on integrating third-party software systems, such as payment systems, ERP, edge computing software for IoT applications. Developed APIs for mobile and pwa applications.

Skills	O	PHP	O	SQL
	0	Git	0	Laravel
	0	Laravel Nova	0	HTML & CSS
		Humanian Nativa anadras		Duraine Native encelor
_anguages	O	Ukranian Native speaker	O	Russian Native speaker
	0	English Highly proficient		

Employment History

Full Stack Developer at Daxx/Grid Dynamics

August 2017 — May 2024

Lead Backend Developer for many projects for Naava Green Walls. Was involved in the development of monitoring systems for the condition of green walls and the development of tools for remote control of watering schedules, lighting and air circulation.

Engaged in API development for https://naava.app/

Full Stack Developer at KnubiSoft

March 2016 — July 2017

Developed various applications from scratch.

Developed subsidiary applications for the Swedish department of the BCA.

Gained development experience using the Falcon framework.

Backend Developer at iDeus

October 2014 — March 2016

Was on the team developing the TesTeachers educational platform, which provides insurance courses for US students.

Was involved in the implementation of the payment system, code refactoring and searching for vulnerabilities in the system.

Full Stack Developer at Mobilluck

May 2013 — October 2014

Worked as part of a team on the site https://www.mobilluck.com.ua/

Was developing tools for sales managers that helped them carry out mass revaluation of items in an online store.

Developed a system for monitoring the items market and revaluation based on the profitability and prices of goods from competitors.

Full Stack Developer at Enrial

January 2013 — May 2013

Developed a business card website for selling car components.

Education

Bachelor, KPI

September 2006 — June 2012

Junior Specialist, KPCC

September 2003 — June 2006

Programming for Computer technology and automated systems

Cover Letter

Throughout my time working on various projects, I had to work on various problems and resort to different approaches to solve them. In development I used frameworks such as Laravel, Lumen, Phalcon, Kohana. I have successfully used programming languages such as PHP(including the latest versions), JavaScript, Python. Developed both MVC projects and APIs for mobile applications and PWA applications. During the development process, I had to deploy projects on platforms such as AWS and GAE. On the projects I worked on, I had to connect third-party services such as NetSuite ERP, ClearBlade, Stripe Payments, etc.

Courses

CSS, jQuery, HTML, JavaScript, Python Core, SQL at Sololearn

Try Ruby, Try Docker, Git Real, Git Real 2, Try Django, Try Git, Try Python, Try SQL at Code School

Links

Github

Codingame

Sololearn

Hobbies

At the moment, my main hobby is athletics. This hobby is the inspiration for developing two pet-projects:

- sport motivation app, based on Strava webhooks;
- voice thranslation for Zombies Run APP, using https://elevenlabs.io/

References

Vadym Antropov(NodeJS developer)

Very good and responsible php programmer. Develops high-loaded projects. Senior level.

Daria Kaidalova (Front-end developer)

I worked with Vadim over 1 year on several projects. He is responsible, professional and accurate teammate. I can highly recommend Vadim as PHP developer.